# SUNDAS SAIFULLAH

An Enthusiastic, Articulate, Goal-Oriented & Well-Presented Marketer who has a successful marketing record in Pharmaceuticals & experience in Entrepreneurship. Highly efficient & currently working as a sole responsible person for promoting Nutraceutical & Gynecologic Portfolio by designing efficient Marketing Strategies & Plans. Can communicate effectively with key decision makers & would find a challenging position in marketing department within an ambitious company, where i will be able to continue to apply my Entrepreneurship Experience & Learnings from Pharmaceutical Industry & develop my abilities.





F.9, Shehzada Plaza, Gul Meher Street, Garden East Karachi 78400



1991-05-24



+923368222466

sundas.saifullah@gmail.com

## **EXPERIENCE**

10.2016 - present

#### Kair Pharma- A member of SJ&G group

Marketing Trainee

Responsibilities: Designing & Developing Marketing Strategies & Plans; Analysis of Sales & IMS regularly. Conducting Seminars; Institutional Presentations on Recent Studies & Product Knowledge. Developing KOLs & Medical Liason; managing events & planning CMEs.

02.2014 - 11.2016

#### **Brand Mafia by Zonash**

Owner

Responsibilities: Start-up of a Brand, promoting & managing the business, studio & workshop comprising of 30 workers. Building trust in the market & among clients.

11.2013 - 02.2014

#### **Text Private Limited**

Health Engagement Specialist

Responsibilities: Managing following Healthcare accounts:

- 1) GETZ Pharma
- 2) Rutgerz WFP

Role: Engaging clients with their key customers with via Software through text messeges; creating blue books for authentic responses of the FAQS; Attending meetings with clients.

06.2012 - 07.2012

#### **Liaguat National Hospital**

Trainee Pharmacist

Responsibilities: As internee Pharmacist attended all lectures and hand-on training in following disciplines:

In-Patient Pharmacy, Out Patient Care Pharmacy Services, Clinical Pharmacy Services, Drug and Poison Information Services, Oncology Pharmacy Services.

05.2011 - 06.2011

#### Ziauddin Hospital

Trainee Pharmacist

Responsibilities: As Intern Pharmacist, worked on dispensing of medicines in In-Patient Pharmacy and Outpatient Pharmacy, formulary formulation, Record keeping, inventory checking & Clinical Rounds

## **OBJECTIVES**

To work in a competant marketing environment in which focused application of marketing & strategic planing will achieve success & exceed the organization's goals & objectives.

# **LANGUAGES**

Enalish



Urdu



Punjabi



## **SKILLS**



Good communication - written and oral skills



Excellent Strategic and Management skills



Efficient Entrepreneur skills



MS Analytical skills

# **PERSONALITY**

Communicative



Punctual



**X** Ambitious



Creative

# **EDUCATION**

2016 - present

College of Business Management, Institute of Business Management

Health & Hospital Management 3.5 GPA

2013 - 2008

Baqai Institute of Pharmaceutical Sciences, Baqai Medical University

Pharm-D 2.8 CGP

2006 - 2008

## Government College for Women, Shahra-e-Liaquat

Higher Secondary School Certificate Grade: B

1996 - 2006

#### St. Lawrence's Convent Girls School

Secondary School Certificate Grade: A

## PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

- Attended a 2 days' workshop at Shaukat Khanam Hospital Karachi, about Oncology practice in Pharmacy- June 2011
- University Visit to GETZ Pharma- 2013.
- Agha Khan Hospital visit by University- 2013.
- 2<sup>nd</sup> National Conference on research in Pharmacy- 2013.
- Seminar on Drug Delivery System in Pakistan- 2013.
- Project on "Live Hospital Pharmacy Setup" 2012.
- Seminar on Communication Skills- 2011
- Workshop on Concept of Pharmacy in Oncology Practice-2011.

## **SOFTWARE SKILLS**

Word



Powerpoint



Microsoft Excel



## **HOBBIES**







Pets

Traveling

O y i